Contact

4048240432 (Mobile) katbuckner09@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/kathleen-buckner-rn-38070783 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Administration
Software Documentation
Nursing

Kathleen Buckner, RN

Registered Nurse at Wellstar Health System Hampton

Summary

Experienced Registered Nurse with a demonstrated history of working in the hospital & health care industry. Skilled in Medical-Surgical, Medication Administration, Medicine, Vital Signs, and U.S. Health Insurance Portability and Accountability Act (HIPAA). Strong healthcare services professional with a Associate's degree focused in Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse from Gordon State College. BLS certified.

Experience

Wellstar Health System
Registered Nurse
July 2019 - Present (1 year 2 months)
United States

Umemployed at this time Registered Nurse March 2019 - July 2019 (5 months)

Homestead Hospice Registered Nurse June 2018 - March 2019 (10 months) Jackson, Georgia

I had a case load of 12-15 patients I visited each week to provide nursing care to.

Eternal Hope
On call Registered Nurse & Case Manager
April 2018 - April 2018 (1 month)
Griffin, Georgia

During orientation was laid off due to census.

Brightmoor Hospice
On call Registered Nurse

February 2017 - December 2017 (11 months)

Griffin, Georgia

Southern Regional Medical Center

Registered Nurse

May 2014 - February 2017 (2 years 10 months)

Med surg. & observation unit

Gastro Specialists of Dekalb

Registered Nurse

December 2012 - September 2013 (10 months)

Decatur, Georgia

IV Administration, charting and monitoring vital signs, assisting physician during upper/lower endoscopies, preparing specimens to be sent to lab, obtaining patient health history before procedures, make follow up calls to assure patients had no concerns, educating patients, recovering patients after procedure and discharging patients.

Doctors Hospice of Georgia

Registered Nurse

April 2011 - October 2011 (7 months)

Reported and monitored significant changes in the condition of the patient, responded and identified the needs of the patient and family, provided emotional support to the patient and the family. Educated and managed LPN and CNA's.

Upson Regional Medical Center

Registered Nurse

July 2010 - November 2010 (5 months)

Thomaston, Georgia

Provided bedside care, treatment and clinical documentation for patients on medical-surgical floor. Handled medication administration, dressing changes, IV's and all other aspects of nursing care. Facilitated admissions, discharges and transfers; prepared chart notes and other documentation.

Education

Gordon State College

Associate's degree, Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse · (2004 - 2009)

Russell High School General Studies · (1982 - 1986)

Russell High East point, ga